Blood pressure app 60 point appointment from 17832 around,
let's reduce and
start giving quicks, Baba ji, tell me about your traits,
time, yes, good morning, you, the one I like
is ICICI General Insurance
and it should be bought here, the target here will be 1160, the
stop will be 1135, ICICI General
Insurance and you should pay attention today, OK
forty, the call went on the screen,
ICICI,
OK, Prakashan's call will be Rajesh
Shatbhuti ji will pick you,
my focus is on Aurobindo Pharma, I think
after the results there was a widening, but this
gap is getting filled, currently
it is trading above 50, so
buy from this and in D Pharma, your stop loss should be
435 and as I said earlier,
75 480 is its target which is pending,
so buy from this, that strategy is available in
front, so it's on
Aurobindo Pharma, see my Pharma space
at 448 60, what will be Mana Saheb's trick,
Virendra ji, PVR looks interesting
because  Consolidation was being seen here, the
new range was getting narrow
but today somewhere a
break out was seen in PVR above ₹1700 on the intraday chart,
so we will
buy PVR on the current news and
your stop loss will be at 1684 or so but
look at the range on the upside till 1775, let me go
ok, good special movie on PVR,
almost 2% up in PVR, market is still around 575
down on Nifty Ashish Chaturmua ji, I like your
pic
[music], the
opposition is
very good, the breakup of Poland flag has been
given by Foods at 512, I think
495 is a very strong support here, so
one should buy this top from 490 test top